Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Junior Sister.
الأخت الصغرى.
We're running low on medicine.
نحن نعاني من نقص في الأدوية.
You should rest well here.
ينبغي عليك أن ترتاح جيدا هنا.
I'll go to the West Market
سأذهب إلى السوق الغربي
to get more medicine.
للحصول على المزيد من الدواء.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
I'm much better now.
أنا أفضل بكثير الآن.
Escorting the Huoshu Yinhua to the Human-Demon Boundary
مرافقة Huoshu Yinhua إلى حدود الإنسان والشيطان
will take quite some time.
سوف يستغرق بعض الوقت.
I'm worried your body won't hold up.
أنا قلق من أن جسدك لن يصمد.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
what you told me yesterday?
ماذا قلت لي بالأمس؟
Of course I remember.
بالطبع أتذكر.
After this escort mission is complete,
بعد اكتمال مهمة المرافقة هذه،
I will marry you.
سأتزوجك
Really?
حقًا؟
What Li Wubai didn't expect was
ما لم يتوقعه لي ووباي هو
Chen Jiang and Wu Hu didn't trust him
تشين جيانج و وو هو لم يثقوا به
and made their move while he was away.
وقاموا بالتحرك أثناء غيابه.
By the time he returned,
وبحلول الوقت الذي عاد فيه،
Liu Yiyi had already misunderstood,
لقد أساء ليو ييي الفهم بالفعل،
thinking he also wanted to steal the Fire Tree Silver Flower.
ظن أنه يريد أيضًا سرقة زهرة شجرة النار الفضية.
Li Wubai.
لي وباي.
Hahaha!
هاهاها!
So,
لذا،
are you surprised?
هل انت متفاجئ؟
At that time, Li Wubai intended to control his strength
في ذلك الوقت، كان لي ووباي ينوي السيطرة على قوته
and just knock Liu Yiyi unconscious temporarily.
وأفقد ليو ييي وعيه مؤقتًا.
To get away with it.
للتخلص من ذلك.
But unexpectedly, the Fire Tree Silver Flower suddenly took effect.
ولكن بشكل غير متوقع، فجأة بدأت زهرة النار الفضية في التأثير.
So, Li Wubai,
لذا، لي وباي،
your purpose for coming to Yuhu Manor
غرضك من المجيء إلى Yuhu Manor
is only one thing:
هو شيء واحد فقط:
to avenge Liu Yiyi from years ago.
للانتقام من ليو ييي منذ سنوات.
You just didn't expect
لم تكن تتوقع ذلك
that she would become the master of the Liu Manor.
أنها سوف تصبح سيدة قصر ليو.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Yiyi.
ييي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I misunderstood you.
لقد اساءت فهمك.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Yiyi.
ييي.
The Huoshu Yinhua took me away.
أخذني Huoshu Yinhua بعيدًا.
It used my obsession
لقد استخدمت هوسي
to absorb countless souls.
لاستيعاب عدد لا يحصى من النفوس.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Kill me.
اقتلني.
No!
لا!
I can barely control it anymore.
بالكاد أستطيع السيطرة عليه بعد الآن.
Do it.
افعلها.
Do it now.
افعلها الآن.
Yiyi.
ييي.
Senior.
كبير.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Senior.
كبير.
When this mission is over,
عندما تنتهي هذه المهمة،
I'll marry you.
سأتزوجك
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Dongfang, are you okay?
دونغفانغ، هل أنت بخير؟
So many sky lanterns.
الكثير من الفوانيس السماوية.
Look at that one,
انظر إلى هذا،
it's flying so high.
إنه يطير عاليا جدا.
It's beautiful.
إنه جميل.
What's wrong with your hand?
ما المشكلة في يدك؟
Does it still hurt from last time?
هل لا زال يؤلمك من المرة السابقة؟
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Madam Ling.
السيدة لينغ.
What's wrong with Dongfang?
ما هو الخطأ في دونغفانغ؟
You know something, don't you?
أنت تعرف شيئا، أليس كذلك؟
Will Dongfang ever wake up?
هل سيستيقظ دونغفانغ يومًا ما؟
Everything is predestined.
كل شيء مقدر.
I don't believe in fate.
أنا لا أؤمن بالقدر.
Madam Ling.
السيدة لينغ.
Don't beat around the bush.
لا تدور حول الموضوع.
You know how to save Dongfang, right?
أنت تعرف كيفية إنقاذ دونغفانغ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
Please save him.
من فضلك انقذه.
Will you?
سوف تفعل؟
Feiye.
تين.
The karmic fire on you
النار الكرمية عليك
is almost gone, isn't it?
لقد انتهى تقريبا، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Why has the karmic fire on me
لماذا النار الكرمية عليّ؟
been disappearing so quickly lately?
هل اختفيت بسرعة كبيرة في الآونة الأخيرة؟
While Dongfang suddenly ended up like this.
في حين انتهى دونغفانغ فجأة بهذا الشكل.
Why is this happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
Dugu Qiongqi did this on purpose.
لقد فعل دوجو تشيونغتشي هذا عمدًا.
The karmic fire doesn't just disappear for no reason.
لا تختفي النار الكرمية فجأة بدون سبب.
It was transferred through the Wujian Vine.
تم نقله عبر Wujian Vine.
The backlash was directed at Dongfang Zhaobai.
وكان رد الفعل العنيف موجها نحو دونغفانغ تشاوباي.
Once the demon vine spreads throughout his body,
بمجرد أن ينتشر كرمة الشيطان في جميع أنحاء جسده،
he will take your place
سوف يأخذ مكانك
and be reduced to ashes.
وتتحول إلى رماد.
What?
ماذا؟
What's in the past
ما في الماضي
should be left in the past.
ينبغي تركه في الماضي.
In the days to come,
في الأيام القادمة،
please take good care of yourself.
من فضلك اعتني بنفسك جيدا.
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
I don't want to trade your life for all this.
لا أريد أن أستبدل حياتك بكل هذا.
Ling Po.
لينغ بو.
If I go back to the past,
إذا عدت إلى الماضي،
kill Dugu Qiongqi,
اقتل دوجو تشيونجكي,
could I change everything?
هل بإمكاني تغيير كل شيء؟
Absolutely not.
بالتأكيد لا.
You must not interfere with your own fate.
لا يجوز لك التدخل في مصيرك.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
a thousand years of effort will be wasted.
سوف تضيع ألف سنة من الجهد.
Just tell me,
فقط أخبرني
is there such a possibility?
هل هناك مثل هذا الاحتمال؟
Feiye.
تين.
Your obsession with the past
هوسك بالماضي
wouldn't it betray
ألا يعتبر ذلك خيانة؟
Dongfang's deep love for you?
ما هو حب دونغفانغ العميق لك؟
Ling Po.
لينغ بو.
You know me better than anyone.
أنت تعرفني أفضل من أي شخص آخر.
You know.
أنت تعرف.
No matter what,
مهما كان الأمر،
I must save him.
يجب أن أنقذه.
Please take care of Dongfang for me.
من فضلك اعتني بـ دونغفانغ من أجلي.
Dongfang
دونغفانغ
wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Miss,
يفتقد،
are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
I made a mistake.
لقد ارتكبت خطأ.
You're not him.
أنت لست هو.
Miss.
يفتقد.
This is not an ordinary inn.
هذا ليس نزلًا عاديًا.
If you want to stay,
إذا كنت تريد البقاء،
you should go elsewhere.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب إلى مكان آخر.
It's getting late now.
لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا الآن.
Evil spirits often appear nearby.
غالبا ما تظهر الأرواح الشريرة في مكان قريب.
Why don't you stay here tonight?
لماذا لا تبقى هنا الليلة؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
let me tell you about our rules.
دعني أخبرك عن قواعدنا.
That won't be necessary.
لن يكون ذلك ضروريا.
I'm very familiar with this place.
أنا أعرف هذا المكان جيداً.
[Key card access]
[الوصول بالبطاقة الرئيسية]
Room cards are more convenient.
بطاقات الغرف أكثر ملاءمة.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Have you been to this inn before?
هل سبق لك زيارة هذا النزل من قبل؟
You seem very familiar with how things work here.
يبدو أنك على دراية كبيرة بكيفية عمل الأشياء هنا.
I've been here for many years
لقد كنت هنا لسنوات عديدة
but don't recall ever seeing you.
ولكنني لا أتذكر رؤيتك من قبل.